<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>DeaDvey</title>
      <link>https://deadvey.com</link>
      <description>Just talking about life and stuff I guess</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 10:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 10:00:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
         <title>Macbeth, Macbeth, where art thou Macbeth?</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/17.html</link>
         <description>I hate Macbeth, I got English Lit exam tommorow on him and then I will NEVER have to think about that bloke every again! Also Christmas Carol but that isn&#39;t as bad as Shakespeare *shudder* the exam will be hellish though so &gt;:( yeah ok, this was a short one,, just a rant I suppose&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/macbeth.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 10:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>macbeth</category><category>english</category><category>exam</category><category>gcse</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Kingdom of the Planet of the Apes - 3/5</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/16.html</link>
         <description>The film had a slow start but I really liked the whole half an hour or so with the orangutang, I thought that was very interesting how different groups had different interpretations on what Ceasers message was. I don&#39;t think I fully understood the ending however, I must watch it again to fully understand it.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/kotpota.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>review</category><category>3 stars</category><category>cinema watch</category><category>family watch</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Exam Stress</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/15.html</link>
         <description>Going into my first written GCSE tommorow (RE Islam) and am quite stressed, heck, I should be doing revision as I type this but I am not because I can&#39;t really be bothered.  I began making a 2D minecraft and dwarf fortress inspired game, I&#39;ve got the world generation done, I&#39;ll upload it to gitlab later probably, I also am trying out Fedora currently, I think it&#39;s pretty decent, some annoyances however, no YaST for one and protonvpn just does not work at all so I haven&#39;t played GTAV in a few days. Today was my first day before exams so a lot of people were stressed and me likewise, I guess it will be over in just over a month so D: Anyway I should do a pastpaper now, maybe go over mitosis, oh god this is so boring! Also, my neighbour wished me luck on my &lt;u&gt;O Levels&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 8 May 2024 16:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>gcse</category><category>exam</category><category>fedora</category><category>minedwarves</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Seven Psychopaths</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/14.html</link>
         <description>I just watched Seven Psychopaths and I thought it was pretty good, I liked how it was structured as the film being the film he is writing (kind of?) and I wrote a short review of it on letterboxd: Actually very good, the final shootout was sick and the film was pretty funny even though quite brutal.&lt;br/&gt;3.5 Stars&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/7psycos.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 4 May 2024 17:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>seven psychopaths</category><category>review</category><category>film</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Mocks over, only GCSE&#39;s to go...</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/13.html</link>
         <description>Just finshed my mocks so will take a day or two off revision, I think I did pretty well, I got 9s in the sciences, I cleaned up my room and organised my cables which was fun, now I&#39;m just listening to music and writing this I guess.  I tried setting up stableLM the other day and failed :(. Today I had an issue with focusing in kde6 where when I clicked a window in the overview, focus was not shifted to that, I fixed this by changing focus behaviour to &#39;Focus under mouse&#39; and that worked, now I have a gnome-like window management in kde6 which I like, I also tried to get jellyfin-mpv-shim to pass the media information through to kde so I can control it from the media controls which would be nice, and I could see the album covers, I couldn&#39;t figure it out, and the only clients that seem to support client casting is the official client and webclient, which pisses me off because I like the look of Tauon Box but it doesn&#39;t let me play and control music on the mpv-shim &gt;:(.  I also played a lot of Fifa 19 and got promoted to the premier leauge so that&#39;s nice. I rewatched (and reread) V for Vendetta, now I&#39;m rewatching Dark Crystal the original film one, not the awful Netflix series, anyway, you can see my reviews for them on letterboxd I suppose, I&#39;m planning on making my blog auto upload my letterboxd reviews, that would be cool. I think that&#39;s all for today ig&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>dark crystal</category><category>letterboxd</category><category>v for vendetta</category><category>stablelm</category><category>jellyfin</category><category>tidy</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Mocks next week and sorry for no updates!</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/12.html</link>
         <description>I&#39;ve been revising (and procrastinating) a LOT over the last month or two and I got mock exams next week in preperation for the May exams so that&#39;s why I&#39;ve not updated this page much, I saw a football game, that was fun, I also watched a lot of films and reviews on Letterboxd, like Dune part 2 which came out a few days ago,would reccoment. I also started reading Agnes Grey yesterday, it&#39;s interesting, I like it so far! anyway, I gotta sleep now, it&#39;s freezing, my boiler broke :(&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 3 Mar 2024 22:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>mocks</category><category>football</category><category>bored</category><category>revision</category><category>agnes grey</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Naught to say</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/11.html</link>
         <description>I havent really done much other than set up my server in my bedroom now and attempted to automate something in selenium, didn&#39;t work but eh.  I&#39;ve been mostly revising so not much to say, oh and a kind of surround sound system for my PS2 I guess&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 23:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>PS2</category><category>surround sound</category><category>bored</category><category>but nothing happened</category><category>the merciless iced east winds that knive us</category><category>condensation polymerisation</category><category>Beneath his hands which did not tremble then, though seem to now</category><category>Lnew = (Loriginal*D^2original)/D^2new</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>H.I.V.E book review (Heavy spoilers)</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/10.html</link>
         <description>I&#39;ve just finished re-reading the H.I.V.E book series, including the last book which realesed, rather delayed, in 2021 (not that I knew at the time), this book series I remember reading when I was about 10 (ish) and I loved reading it, the newest book adds a satifying, if slightly odd conclusion to the series.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 1: The Higher Institute Of Villainous Education, the first book in the series, and you can really tell, (comparitively) low stakes as we see the main 4 characters introduced to a school of villainy and attempt an escape.  I thought the escape method felt unique and refreshing as opposed to some escape books/media I have consumed, and they don&#39;t even suceed.  Instanly after their failed attempt, the school is attacked by a giant man-eating plant called &#39;Violet&#39; it was nice to see that the plant was built up to and foreshadowed earlier on, but it did also feel like it was tacked on at the end and generally doesn&#39;t have much sifnificance to the rest of the books. &lt;br/&gt;Book 2: Overlord Protocol, this is where the story really begins, the introductions are done so now the series can truly begin.  In this one we see a character named Cypher attempt to take over the school, at first he seems like just a generic villain whos power hungry, however, it is revealed that it is in fact Wing&#39;s father and he is attempting to take out an old failed AI experiment called &#39;Overlord&#39; who is threatening world domination.  This was an interestng one, much more action than the original, I don&#39;t think we were attatched enough to the character of The Contessa to feel betrayed when its revealed she is working with Cypher, I also think the ending is satisfying, as we begin to cast doubt on the supreme Number 1.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 3: Escape Velocity, I like to think of this as the ending of the original trilogy of books (with there being 3 trilogies throughout) and a satisfying ending as well, it starts with the head teacher (Nero) being captured by a new organisation known as H.O.P.E, the school is then taken over by the Contessa and the main four characters escape the school to save Nero, they must break into MI6 in order to find Nero&#39;s location and they save him, then they go into space to defeat Number One (Overlord) thinking it&#39;s the last of him.  I thought this one was very well done with suitably high stakes and a nicely dramatic ending, I also thought the mystery was well done and the MI6 infiltraction bit was really fun.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 4: Dreadnaught, Darkdoom is the new leader of G.L.O.V.E and some people are not happy, a new organisation called the Disiples and a former member of G.L.O.V.E, Jason Drake take over The Dreadnaught and plan to nuke Yellowstone National Park, luckily, with 9 seconds to spare Otto manages to cancel the nuke and save the world.  I loved the dramatic ending and the repercusions of this one, the stakes are very big (nice) although the rest of the book falls a little flat for me, not bad by any means, but the ending makes up for it.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 5: Rouge, as a consequence of stopping the nuke, Otto is captured by the US government and sent to H.O.P.E where they use a new bio machine called the animus to control Otto, this is why I like to call this the Animus trilogy, the main characters save Otto from the H.O.P.E facility and Cypher (finally) dies.  I thought this one was OK, felt a bit filler though and the stakes wheren&#39;t super high (comparitively, I mean H.O.P.E was still trying to assassinate Nero so).  &lt;br/&gt;Book 6: Zero Hour, a phenomenal book, massive stakes, massive lot peices, massive consequesnces, Nero goes to England to initiate Zero Hour after Overlord fully returns, a plan to stop any villain on the brink of world domination, however Otto is captured by Overlord and a possessed Raven and are taken to the AWP facilty, though Nero and Darkdoom soon arrive with an army of old Alpha stream students to take out Overlord, they manage to succeed in the end but Lucy dies and Otto has to ask the president of the United States to nuke the AWP facility to eradicate Overlord and the Animus swarm.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 7: Aftershock, this is my personal favourite, even though the stakes aren&#39;t that high, there&#39;s a lot of action packed parts and it&#39;s a really good one.  The characters go on a missio called the hunt, however, the locationof the Hunt has been leaked to the Disiples by a mysterious insider at H.I.V.E who masacre loads of Alpha stream students, Raven and the main characters (now a sizeable group) manage to escape and have a final stand aganst the Disiples in Siberia before revealing that Laura (and Cheif Dekker) were the informants, though Laura was blackmailed, it also truns out that the leader of the Disiples is Anastasia Furan, Pietor&#39;s sister and shes out for blood, Anastasia is pure evil in this and it&#39;s kind of terrifying.  I loved this one in particular because there is no happy ending, it works as a great duo with the next book, Deadlock, and is great, Laura Penny, Tom and Nigel get captured by Anastasia and taken to the Glasshouse. &lt;br/&gt; Book 8: Deadlock, the penultimate book, and until not long ago was the final book, I was always annoyed at how it ended on a cliffhanger, assuming the author would never release the final book but now that he has, I can see how good the ending is. They must track down Anastasia&#39;s glasshouse and Raven and the now expelled Otto are tying to track her down, they find &#39;The Architect&#39; who turns out to be Neros father and using the design, Lauras hacked message in a bottle and Otto crossed with H.I.V.E.mind&#39;s derypting manage to find the glasshouse and go on a rescue mission, Otto meets his clone who tries to kill him, but H.I.V.E.mind helps kill the clone and Otto dupes Anastasia as she thinks he is the clone, they manage to capture Anastaia (just) and free the captured students, Anastasia is locked up.  I really loved the bit where Otto tricks Anastasia but Raven knows its him, so good, all in all, this is my second favourite book in the series, a reall thriller.  &lt;br/&gt;Book 9(finale): Bloodline, wow I have mixed feelings about this, I was waiting a while for this to come out and I was quite exited when I found out it had, there are some really weird decisions made with character design and Penny feels really like a missed opputunitu, having said that, it was really good and Ottos sacrifice at the end is so good, though I don&#39;t understand why they brought Otto back to life, just leave him dead, make his sacrifice more meaningful!  Another clone of Otto manages to hack into H.I.V.E&#39;s system and lock them out the gain control of Cyphers robots, she takes over the school and an all out attack is made by the protagonists, they nearly fail, but Otto injects the last bit of the Animus into him and manages to defeat the clone temporarily, but he needs to nuke the school to take her out forever, so he does that with him in it, a meaningful sacrifice.  &lt;br/&gt;All in all it was a great series, and this is how my current ranking goes: 1.Aftershock, 2.Deadlock, 3.Zero Hour, 4.Bloodline, 5.Dreadnaught, 6.Escape Velocity, 7.Overlord Protocol, 8.Rougue, 9.Higher blah di blah, although I don&#39;t actually think any are bad, my opinion on Bloodline might change though as I quite literally just finished it like half an hour ago. &lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hive.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 22:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>H.I.V.E</category><category>HIVE</category><category>Book Review</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Sorry for inactivity</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/9.html</link>
         <description>As the title says, I haven&#39;t really had much to talk about as I&#39;ve just been revising mostly, but I have been using more of my Raspberry Pi, I&#39;m also on book 6/9 of &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.goodreads.com/series/43743-h-i-v-e&#39;&gt;H.I.V.E (Higher Institute of Villainous Education)&lt;/a&gt;  which I&#39;m re reading right now. I have built the rocket silo in &lt;a href=&#39;https://factorio.com&#39;&gt;Factorio&lt;/a&gt; but have not launched it. Oh yeah, and I began implementing comments, but they don&#39;t work yet so I guess that might work in the future, possibly... Other than that I&#39;ve not done much&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/factorio.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hive.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 15:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>HIVE</category><category>raspberry</category><category>pi</category><category>revision</category><category>factorio</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Henry Stickmin completion</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/8.html</link>
         <description>This week I have been playing a lot (and have 100%ed) of Henry Stickmin which has been really fun, I also bingewatched &lt;a href=&#39;https://yewtu.be/watch?v=OcLU07tnfv4&#39;&gt;2 left thumbs&#39; youtube series&lt;/a&gt; about references in the remastered versions, I played the first few games a years ago when I watched DanTDM&#39;s series, and the new ones have a lot better graphics, but they&#39;re all great.  I&#39;ve also been re reeading a book series I used to be obsessed with called &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.goodreads.com/series/43743-h-i-v-e&#39;&gt;H.I.V.E&lt;/a&gt; which has been a blast and I&#39;m exited as a new book released last year but I haven&#39;t read it.  This week (I beleive) Hyprland overtook Sway in terms of stars on Github, which is exiting.  I have not come to a decision about adding comments to my blog posts, but if I did, they would be pretty simple, no logins, just type your name and the comment, then I can respond to it if I see it; pretty simple.  I&#39;m going to be getting my braces out in about 6 weeks time and using retainers, so I&#39;m looking forward to that :D.  Yeah, there&#39;s not much to talk about really, I&#39;m just anticipating the end of the Winter break tommorow (today is insect day) really.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey 🥱&lt;img src=&quot;/images/henry-stickmin.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/hyprland-vs-sway.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 8 Jan 2024 16:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>henry stickmin</category><category>HIVE</category><category>comments</category><category>hyprland</category><category>sway</category><category>braces</category><category>bored</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Happy New Year!!!!</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/7.html</link>
         <description>Firstly, Happy new year everyone, I was planning on doing this yesterday, but got distracted, I don&#39;t know about any of you, but mine is 1080p, I don&#39;t like 4K because I find things like the cursor don&#39;t scale well on a 4K monitor in KDE and in a tty the text is super small on 4K! Email me your new years resolutions, I&#39;d love to know: &lt;a href=&#39;mailto:email@deadvey.xyz&#39;&gt;email@deadvey.xyz&lt;/a&gt;.  Secondly, I have discovered a new Terminal Emulator caleld &lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/borisfaure/terminology&#39;&gt;Terminology&lt;/a&gt;, now it&#39;s quite heavy, so not really for anyone who likes lighter ones like Alacritty or Xterm, but it&#39;s really fancy and has optional backgrounds and overlays, and a cool bell that rings if you backspace too far back, I&#39;m really liking it so far but we&#39;ll see, I also have installed a new font for my system which I&#39;m using in Terminology called &lt;a href=&#39;https://rubjo.github.io/victor-mono/&#39;&gt;Victor Mono&lt;/a&gt; which is a monospaced font that has a nice subtle cursive style, I know that&#39;s kinda cursed but I really like it and Capital letters are non cursive so that they can be easier read.  I have found a small (7 inch) screen that is designed for the Raspberry Pi which I might get in order to make a custom laptop for my Pi which will be cool as the VNC route is extremly unstable and laggy as it&#39;s over WiFi, I&#39;ll have a think about it though and I&#39;ll consider the 8 Inch version.  My account has been accepted onto &lt;a href=&#39;https://fossfarmers.company/a/deadvey8383&#39;&gt;Foss farmers Peertube Instance&lt;/a&gt; so I&#39;m now uploading to there, Check that out, though I am also uplaoding to &lt;a href=&#39;/video&#39;&gt;My website&lt;/a&gt;.  I have made a &lt;a href=&#39;https://github.com/DeaDvey/node&#39;&gt;Github repo for the node js of this website&lt;/a&gt; and so this whole site is now public on Github I have made a commit today, I added previous and next links to the blog pages, it checks first if  the post number is not equal to 0 (the first post) then if it is not, it adds a previous link, and if it is not the equal to the length of the array - 1 then it adds a next link, so I think I did it ok, that&#39;s in the makeblogs.js file.  Finally, I have gotten back into the &lt;i&gt;spirit&lt;/i&gt; of revision for the exams coming up since the christmas break where I gave myself a rest, I did some pastpapers and maths today which was &lt;i&gt;fun&lt;/i&gt;.  Okay, that&#39;s it for today, hope you have a good day!&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fireworks.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/terminology.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/farmtube.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Wed, 3 Jan 2024 00:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>new year</category><category>terminology</category><category>victor mono</category><category>resolution</category><category>pi</category><category>montior</category><category>7 inch</category><category>peertube</category><category>node js</category><category>github</category><category>previous</category><category>next</category><category>revision</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Homemade laptop, Nextcloud and possible updates to website</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/6.html</link>
         <description>This week I used my raspberry pi to make a Homemade laptop, for the case I used a cardboard box with a hinge duck taped to the back so it doesn&#39;t flop around.  I used a drawing tablet as a mouse as I had no spare mouse, the monitor is my phone conecting to the raspberry pi through &lt;a href=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_Network_Computing&#39;&gt;VNC&lt;/a&gt; which is very janky and I used a massive portable charger to keep the phone and pi charged, the whole thing is really janky and I want to maybe get a 7 inch monitor for it which would work way better but, that&#39;s for the furture me.  I&#39;ve found a cool new feature on Nextcloud called face recognition, I have not gotton it working though so I&#39;ll try figure that out, I suck at troubleshooting, it took like a week to figure out how to use occ, it&#39;s in the nextcloud root directory ._., there&#39;s also a map fearture which uses &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.openstreetmap.org&#39;&gt;Open Street Maps&lt;/a&gt; to show where images where taken and when and also to plot addresses of your contacts which is very useful.  Finally, I was thinking of added a comment system to my blog posts, but don&#39;t know if I should as it could be vunerable and shit like that and I also can&#39;t really be bothered seeing as no one would use it... On the plus side I got Jotit working on my UBT phone because it needed a bloody / at the end of the address, WHY??? idk it just does for some reason.  Anyway, that&#39;s it for today.&lt;br/&gt; Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/custom_laptop.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/nextcloud_maps.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 20:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Nextcloud</category><category>Website</category><category>VNC</category><category>Laptop</category><category>Maps</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/5.html</link>
         <description>Merry Christmas everyone! Hope everyone is having a great day :), I had an interesting day, I got a Raspberry Pi 4 (4G version) and it&#39;s really cool, I already got &lt;a href=&#39;https://supertuxkart.net/Main_Page&#39;&gt;Super Tux Kart&lt;/a&gt; which is fun, I&#39;ve also connected it to wifi and that&#39;s about it, I got a new keyboard which is way better than my old cheap stiff one, it seems to have helped my wpm, I got a massive power bank which has been charging for 3 hours now and has gone up 18% on the bank, meaning there is A LOT of total power in there :D  Finally, I&#39;ve gotton a new monitor for a grand total of 3 which is nice, I can have firefox on one, music on the other and a game on the third, I love it. I also got a Tux sticker which is super nice and a mug whcih says &#39;number #0 programmer&#39; lol.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/3c/b3/91/3cb39177fe9f33771c961835ac85c754.png&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;image of tux&#39; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/images/supertuxkart.png&#39; alt=&#39;Image of supertux kart&#39; height=&#39;200&#39;/&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 18:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Christmas</category><category>monitor</category><category>keyboard</category><category>sticker</category><category>mug</category><category>power bank</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>RSS feeds and Star Wars Squadrons</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/4.html</link>
         <description>Hey people (person(me)), I just updated my website to have an &lt;a href=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSS&#39;&gt;RSS Feed&lt;/a&gt; so that I can read them in Fluent Reader or Nextcloud News, the two RSS readers I use mostly, I cannot get them all to show up in Nextcloud News however, only the most recent one, maybe an issue with the formating? Ah well, I&#39;ll try troubleshoot that I guess.  Secondly, I recently got the game &lt;a href=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1222730/STAR_WARS_Squadrons/&#39;&gt;Star Wars Squadrons&lt;/a&gt; on my PC after already having played it on my PS4 and I was surprised at the poor reviews, I always found the game really fun and the integrated HUD really fun to use, guess I just am different lol, anyway&lt;br/&gt; Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1222730/header.jpg?t=1662047498&#39; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>RSS</category><category>Sqaudrons</category><category>Star Wars</category><category>News</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Late December Update Before Christmas</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/3.html</link>
         <description>Hey guys, so I have been trying out Nextcloud since I did the last blog and I really like it, it&#39;s very good, the calendar especially, I think I definately prefer it to Proton Drive and Calendar because it&#39;s way better intergreated in to apps and stuff, there&#39;s also apps for it on the Ubuntu Touch store, which lacks Proton apps, the notes are also great as is the RSS reader that I can sync.  Secondly, I have also began watching Attack on Titan again as my freind has been going on about it, I&#39;m readig the Manga but it is so slow, so I&#39;ll probably keep watching the Animé which I like.  Christmas is in a few days and we break up tommorow which is pretty exiting and I&#39;ll see some family, I think I&#39;m getting the &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.raspberrypi.com/products/raspberry-pi-5/&#39;&gt;Raspberry Pi 5&lt;/a&gt; which is cool.  Finally, I got the &lt;a href=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/app/582160/Assassins_Creed_Origins/&#39;&gt;Assassins Creed Origins game&lt;/a&gt; which I already had on PS4 but now I have on Steam because it was on sale, but I can&#39;t get it to work so I&#39;ll have to figure that out over the weekend, anyway, that is probably it for today.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://searx.be/image_proxy?url=https%3A%2F%2Fi.pinimg.com%2F236x%2Fc5%2F7f%2Fe1%2Fc57fe1d506c6a3aa53bd953199b7ea9f.jpg&amp;h=60634c3b8432ca80d66386441593891a87a58ae6ec4810c40a64a665b0e677fc&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;An image of Assassins Creed Origins&#39; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/23551-Raspberry-Pi-5-8G-feature.jpg&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;An image of a Raspberry Pi 5&#39;/&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Christmas</category><category>Raspberry</category><category>pi</category><category>Nextcloud</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>I didn&#39;t like Wordpress</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/2.html</link>
         <description>So... Yeah, I didn&#39;t like wordpress very much, it&#39;s pretty clunky and I don&#39;t have much control over the webpage, and it&#39;s kinda not that fun to use, I&#39;m glad I tried it out though because I kind of know how to use it know I suppose, I might copy over the wordpress back over to this so I can use it myself for fun I suppose.&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wordpress.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Wordpress</category><category>html</category><category>control</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Test post2</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/1.html</link>
         <description>Testicy Test</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Test</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Test post</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/0.html</link>
         <description>Testy test!</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Test</category>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
