<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
   <channel>
      <title>DeaDvey</title>
      <link>https://deadvey.com</link>
      <description>Just talking about life and stuff I guess</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 20:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 20:41:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
         <title>Homemade laptop, Nextcloud and possible updates to website</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/6.html</link>
         <description>This week I used my raspberry pi to make a Homemade laptop, for the case I used a cardboard box with a hinge duck taped to the back so it doesn&#39;t flop around.  I used a drawing tablet as a mouse as I had no spare mouse, the monitor is my phone conecting to the raspberry pi through &lt;a href=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_Network_Computing&#39;&gt;VNC&lt;/a&gt; which is very janky and I used a massive portable charger to keep the phone and pi charged, the whole thing is really janky and I want to maybe get a 7 inch monitor for it which would work way better but, that&#39;s for the furture me.  I&#39;ve found a cool new feature on Nextcloud called face recognition, I have not gotton it working though so I&#39;ll try figure that out, I suck at troubleshooting, it took like a week to figure out how to use occ, it&#39;s in the nextcloud root directory ._., there&#39;s also a map fearture which uses &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.openstreetmap.org&#39;&gt;Open Street Maps&lt;/a&gt; to show where images where taken and when and also to plot addresses of your contacts which is very useful.  Finally, I was thinking of added a comment system to my blog posts, but don&#39;t know if I should as it could be vunerable and shit like that and I also can&#39;t really be bothered seeing as no one would use it... On the plus side I got Jotit working on my UBT phone because it needed a bloody / at the end of the address, WHY??? idk it just does for some reason.  Anyway, that&#39;s it for today.&lt;br/&gt; Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/custom_laptop.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/nextcloud_maps.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 20:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Nextcloud</category><category>Website</category><category>VNC</category><category>Laptop</category><category>Maps</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/5.html</link>
         <description>Merry Christmas everyone! Hope everyone is having a great day :), I had an interesting day, I got a Raspberry Pi 4 (4G version) and it&#39;s really cool, I already got &lt;a href=&#39;https://supertuxkart.net/Main_Page&#39;&gt;Super Tux Kart&lt;/a&gt; which is fun, I&#39;ve also connected it to wifi and that&#39;s about it, I got a new keyboard which is way better than my old cheap stiff one, it seems to have helped my wpm, I got a massive power bank which has been charging for 3 hours now and has gone up 18% on the bank, meaning there is A LOT of total power in there :D  Finally, I&#39;ve gotton a new monitor for a grand total of 3 which is nice, I can have firefox on one, music on the other and a game on the third, I love it. I also got a Tux sticker which is super nice and a mug whcih says &#39;number #0 programmer&#39; lol.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/3c/b3/91/3cb39177fe9f33771c961835ac85c754.png&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;image of tux&#39; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/images/supertuxkart.png&#39; alt=&#39;Image of supertux kart&#39; height=&#39;200&#39;/&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 18:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Christmas</category><category>monitor</category><category>keyboard</category><category>sticker</category><category>mug</category><category>power bank</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>RSS feeds and Star Wars Squadrons</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/4.html</link>
         <description>Hey people (person(me)), I just updated my website to have an &lt;a href=&#39;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RSS&#39;&gt;RSS Feed&lt;/a&gt; so that I can read them in Fluent Reader or Nextcloud News, the two RSS readers I use mostly, I cannot get them all to show up in Nextcloud News however, only the most recent one, maybe an issue with the formating? Ah well, I&#39;ll try troubleshoot that I guess.  Secondly, I recently got the game &lt;a href=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/app/1222730/STAR_WARS_Squadrons/&#39;&gt;Star Wars Squadrons&lt;/a&gt; on my PC after already having played it on my PS4 and I was surprised at the poor reviews, I always found the game really fun and the integrated HUD really fun to use, guess I just am different lol, anyway&lt;br/&gt; Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/1222730/header.jpg?t=1662047498&#39; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>RSS</category><category>Sqaudrons</category><category>Star Wars</category><category>News</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Late December Update Before Christmas</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/3.html</link>
         <description>Hey guys, so I have been trying out Nextcloud since I did the last blog and I really like it, it&#39;s very good, the calendar especially, I think I definately prefer it to Proton Drive and Calendar because it&#39;s way better intergreated in to apps and stuff, there&#39;s also apps for it on the Ubuntu Touch store, which lacks Proton apps, the notes are also great as is the RSS reader that I can sync.  Secondly, I have also began watching Attack on Titan again as my freind has been going on about it, I&#39;m readig the Manga but it is so slow, so I&#39;ll probably keep watching the Animé which I like.  Christmas is in a few days and we break up tommorow which is pretty exiting and I&#39;ll see some family, I think I&#39;m getting the &lt;a href=&#39;https://www.raspberrypi.com/products/raspberry-pi-5/&#39;&gt;Raspberry Pi 5&lt;/a&gt; which is cool.  Finally, I got the &lt;a href=&#39;https://store.steampowered.com/app/582160/Assassins_Creed_Origins/&#39;&gt;Assassins Creed Origins game&lt;/a&gt; which I already had on PS4 but now I have on Steam because it was on sale, but I can&#39;t get it to work so I&#39;ll have to figure that out over the weekend, anyway, that is probably it for today.&lt;br/&gt;Fly You High - DeaDvey&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://searx.be/image_proxy?url=https%3A%2F%2Fi.pinimg.com%2F236x%2Fc5%2F7f%2Fe1%2Fc57fe1d506c6a3aa53bd953199b7ea9f.jpg&amp;h=60634c3b8432ca80d66386441593891a87a58ae6ec4810c40a64a665b0e677fc&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;An image of Assassins Creed Origins&#39; /&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/23551-Raspberry-Pi-5-8G-feature.jpg&#39; height=&#39;200&#39; alt=&#39;An image of a Raspberry Pi 5&#39;/&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Christmas</category><category>Raspberry</category><category>pi</category><category>Nextcloud</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>I didn&#39;t like Wordpress</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/2.html</link>
         <description>So... Yeah, I didn&#39;t like wordpress very much, it&#39;s pretty clunky and I don&#39;t have much control over the webpage, and it&#39;s kinda not that fun to use, I&#39;m glad I tried it out though because I kind of know how to use it know I suppose, I might copy over the wordpress back over to this so I can use it myself for fun I suppose.&lt;img src=&quot;/images/wordpress.png&quot; alt=&quot;Blog Image&quot; /&gt;</description>
         <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Wordpress</category><category>html</category><category>control</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Test post2</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/1.html</link>
         <description>Testicy Test</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Test</category>
      </item>
      <item>
         <title>Test post</title>
         <link>https://deadvey.com/blog/blogs/0.html</link>
         <description>Testy test!</description>
         <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
         <category>Test</category>
      </item>
   </channel>
</rss>
